<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Noti Sender</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Noti Sender</string>

    <string name="account">account</string>
    <string name="Login">Log in to Google</string>
    <string name="Logout">Log out to Google</string>
    <string name="UID_default">Not logined</string>

    <string name="serviceToggle">Service on/off</string>

    <string name="select_package">Select App</string>
    <string name="all">send all notifications</string>

    <string name="App_info">App info</string>
    <string name="App_info_des">infos about this app</string>
    <string name="App_info_about">About</string>
    <string name="gotogit">Go to git repo</string>

    <string name="History_title">Notification History</string>

    <string name="tasker_label">Task type</string>
    <string name="tasker_label_des">Task type to execute</string>

    <string name="notify_channel_id">NotiSender</string>
    <string name="notify_channel_name">Noti Sender</string>
    <string name="notify_channel_description">Send notification to another device</string>

    <string name="notiDetail_ok">Remote run</string>
    <string name="notiDetail_cancel">Close</string>

    <string name="dialog_update_title">Update exists</string>
    <string name="dialog_update_message">An update exists. Do you want to update?</string>

    <string name="Server_information">FCM : Also known as Firebase Cloud Messaging, this is a free message push API provided by Google. It is stable and consumes less battery, but pushed messages may not come if pushed messages are delayed or if the device is in deep-sleep mode.\n\nPushy : This is a message push API provided by Pushy.org. It is faster than FCM and does not cause delays, but the performance and battery consumption of the device is high, and it is available only with a paid subscription.</string>
    <string name="Interval_information">"Set the interval for notifications. For example, if an interval of 100ms is set and the notification 'A' appears, no other notification is sent and ignored for 100ms after the 'A' notification appears.\n\nOption details\nEntire app : Treats notifications from all apps as one app and applies intervals.\nPer app : Apply notification interval for each app.\n\n\nNote: This option also applies to sending SMS and Call notifications.</string>
    <string name="Encryption_information">When sending/receiving data, AES-128 is used to protect users\' personal information.\n\nIn addition, the key to be used for encryption entered and set by the user is encrypted once more using a token assigned to each user provided by Google.\n\nCaution 1. Noti Sender\'s development team (Norix Team) is not responsible for anything that happens due to the disclosure of the security key or the entire data.\n\nCaution 2. If encryption is set, the encrypted Notification data may be too large to send, and in this case, the data will not be transmitted.\n\nCaution 3. If encryption is enabled, no icon is sent even if the Send Icon option is turned on.\n\nCaution 4. Encryption works only for FCM and does not work for Pushy server. </string>
    <string name="Dialog_rather_github">Due to the suppression of SMS &amp; Call log access permission by Google Play policy, you need to download Noti Sender from Github rather than Play store to use this function.</string>
    <string name="Dialog_Tasker_compatible">Plugins are available in the apps shown below.\n\n - Tasker\n(net.dinglisch.android.taskerm)\n\n - Automate\n(com.llamalab.automate)\n\n - Locale X\n(com.twofortyfouram.locale.x)\n\n - MacroDroid\n(com.arlosoft.macrodroid)</string>
    <string name="Premium_information">NotiSender Premium comes with the following benefits:\n\n - Increased the file size limit to 2GB when transferring files to other devices\n - Can pair more than 3 devices\n - Use album art when remotely controlling media\n - Can add 3 or more custom regex objects\n - Use Pushy server for data transfer\n\nBenefits may be added or reduced without notice and do not apply to NotiSender for desktop.</string>
    <string name="Premium_waring">\n\nPlease subscribe NotiSender Premium and try again!\n\nTip: You can subscribe at \"Service &amp; Account\" menu.</string>

    <string name="updater_loading">Loading… Please wait</string>
    <string name="updater_checkupdate">Checking update…</string>
    <string name="updater_manager_deprecated_title">Found deprecated app</string>
    <string name="updater_manager_deprecated_message">Since the Manager and the main app have been reintegrated, Noti Sender Manager (com.noti.sender) is deprecated and no longer needed. \n\nYou can delete manager if you wish. Are you want to delete Manager?</string>
    <string name="Start_Activity_Completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="ServiceToggle">Service On/Off</string>
    <string name="edit_item">Edit Items</string>
    <string name="playground">Playground</string>

    <string name="media_play">Play</string>
    <string name="media_pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="media_previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="media_next">Next</string>
    <string name="media_close">Close</string>
</resources>
